<resources>
    <string name="app_name">INFS3605_Group_Assignment</string>
    <string name="faq1">
        <b>What is the Gather App?</b>
        <br /> Gather provides a place to record and organise climate change related findings, interacts with other citizen scientists,
        and keep up to date about climate change in Australia. It encourages the participation of citizen scientists
        including, but not limited to, First Nations people, hikers, and ecologists.
        Through cataloguing these first-hand experiences of Australia’s climate,
        Gather hopes to create an extensive database of the impacts of climate change
        \n
        </string>

    <string name="faq2">
        <b>How do I contact Gather or send feedback?</b>
        You can contact us at help@gather.com
    </string>

    <string name="faq3">
        <b>How do my donations help?</b>
        Your donations help support the work of various charities that we have identified that support climate change action.<br />
    </string>

    <string name="faq4">
        <b>Can I use photos and videos that are posted on Gather?</b>
        Gather does not own the photos or videos that our users post here, they belong to the people who upload them. By default, all photos and videos to Gather are released under a Create Commons Attribution Non Commercial License.
        </string>

    <string name="faq5">
        <b>What technologies and data sources does this project use?</b>
        Gather is build using Java, and Firebase Realtime database.
        </string>

    <string-array name="textActivityTypes">
        <item>Select Post</item>
        <item>Image</item>
        <item>Video</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="imageActivityTypes">
        <item>Select Post</item>
        <item>Text</item>
        <item>Video</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="videoActivityTypes">
        <item>Select Post</item>
        <item>Text</item>
        <item>Image</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="newsTitles">
        <item>An observation made on New Climate driver</item>
        <item>New limits placed on creation</item>
        <item>Update 3.0</item>
        <item>Changing new policies</item>
        <item>Update 2.0</item>
        <item>Update 1.0</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="newsDesc">
        <item>For some time now, Gather has included the following data points to identify causes linked to the bushfires in South Australia...</item>
        <item>Starting next week, we need your help to identify opinions on the South Australian Bush fire and what we could have changed...</item>
        <item>A new update to fix upload glitches...</item>
        <item>Thanks for everyones posts! Recent data has been used by the Australian Government in their budget for industries lacking Climate Support</item>
        <item>You can now post videos and photos...</item>
        <item>A new update to fix upload glitches...</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>